(birds singing,
insects trilling)
SHELDON:
It's nice to get back to nature.
(Sheldon:)Why don't I do this more often?
(Sheldon:)What a beautiful forest.
(gasps delightedly)
(Sheldon:)Hello, little butterfly.
(Sheldon:)What's your Na...
(screams)
(Leonard:)Whatcha doing?
(Sheldon:)I was enjoying
some virtual reality,
(Sheldon:)until you ruined it
with your actual face.
(Penny:)What am I smelling?
(Sheldon:)Oh, it's car
air freshener.
(Sheldon:)I was simulating
the smell of the forest.
(Penny:)That's not what
the forest smells like.
(Sheldon:)Well, how would I know?
(Leonard:)Why are you pretending
to be outdoors?
(Leonard:)You hate it.
(Sheldon:)Hmm? Oh.
(Sheldon:)Amy showed me a compelling study
(Sheldon:)that demonstrated
the cognitive benefit
(Sheldon:)of spending time
in the wilderness.
(Leonard:)Buddy, I am ready
to drive you
(Leonard:)into the wilderness
any time you want
(Leonard:)and leave you there.
(Sheldon:)Well, make your jokes,
but some of the participants
(Sheldon:)who spent four days in the woods
away from all technology
reported a 50% gain in reasoning
skills upon their return.
(Penny:)Okay, if that's true, why aren't
there more genius squirrels?
(Sheldon:)You may need this
more than I do.
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪